cloud66.com 2019-08-25

# Cloud 66 · Privacy Policy

The **“I’m like you”** version 

By accessing or using Cloud 66, you agree to be bound by this Policy and our Terms of Service

We use cookies to collect anonymised web traffic on our site. We also store all information you’ve given us about yourself and your servers, jobs and schedules on our secure servers and as secure as possible.

### What do we do with your data?

Your data belongs to you and we do not sell or lend any part of your data to any third party. This excludes legal obligations to government bodies in various jurisdictions

### What happens to your data when you leave Cloud 66? 

We delete everything we have on our servers about you, your servers and your apps permanently. We might hold on to your name and email address so we can contact you later

We fully comply with the European General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) laws, requirements and regulations. If you have any questions regarding this please contact [privacy@cloud66.com](mailto:privacy@cloud66.com?subject=GDPR)

The **“I’m a lawyer”** version 

  * Information we may collect from you
  * IP Addresses and Cookies
  * Where we store your personal data
  * Uses made of the information
  * Disclosure of your information
  * Your Rights
  * Access to Information
  * Changes to our privacy policy
  * Contact

[Cloud 66](http://www.cloud66.com/) (“We”) are committed to protecting and respecting your privacy. This policy (together with Terms and Conditions and any other documents referred to on it) sets out the basis on which any personal data we collect from you, or that you provide to us, will be processed by us. Please read the following carefully to understand our views and practices regarding your personal data and how we will treat it.

We keep certain basic information when you visit our website and recognise the importance of keeping that information secure and letting you know what we will do with it. For the purpose of the Data Protection Act 1998 (the Act), the data controller is [Cloud 66](http://www.cloud66.com/). 

This policy only applies to our site. If you leave our site via a link or otherwise, you will be subject to the policy of that website provider. We have no control over that policy or the terms of the website and you should check their policy before continuing to access the site.

### Information we may collect from you

We may collect and process the following data about you:

  * Information that you provide by filling in forms on our site cloud66.com (our site). This includes information provided at the time of registering to use our site, subscribing to our service or requesting further services. We may also ask you for information when you report a problem with our site.
  * If you contact us, we may keep a record of that correspondence.
  * We may also ask you to complete surveys that we use for research purposes, although you do not have to respond to them.
  * Details of your visits to our site including, but not limited to, traffic data, location data, weblogs, operating workspace, browser usage and other communication data, whether this is required for our own billing purposes or otherwise and the resources that you access.

### IP Addresses and Cookies

We may collect information about your computer, including where available your IP address, operating workspace and browser type, for workspace administration and to report aggregate information to our advertisers. This is statistical data about our users’ browsing actions and patterns, and does not identify any individual and we will not collect personal information in this way.

We may obtain information about your general internet usage by using a cookie file which is stored on the hard drive of your computer. Cookies contain information that is transferred to your computer’s hard drive. They help us to improve our site and to deliver a better and more personalised service. They enable us:

  * To estimate our audience size and usage pattern.
  * To store information about your preferences, and so allow us to customise our site according to your individual interests.
  * To speed up your searches.
  * To recognise you when you return to our site.

You may refuse to accept cookies by activating the setting on your browser which allows you to refuse the setting of cookies. However, if you select this setting you may be unable to access certain parts of our site. Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our workspace will issue cookies when you log on to our site.

### Where we store your personal data

The data that we collect from you may be transferred to, and stored at, a destination outside the European Economic Area (“EEA”). It may also be processed by staff operating outside the EEA who work for us or for one of our suppliers. Such staff maybe engaged in, among other things, the fulfilment of your order, the processing of your payment details and the provision of support services. By submitting your personal data, you agree to this transfer, storing or processing.

We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this privacy policy. All information you provide to us is stored on our secure servers. Any payment transactions will be encrypted. Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password which enables you to access certain parts of our site, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share a password with anyone. Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. 

Although we will do our best to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to our site; any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your information, we will use strict procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorized access.

### Uses made of the information

We use information held about you in the following ways:

  * To ensure that content from our site is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your computer.
  * To provide you with information, products or services that you request from us or which we feel may interest you, where you have consented to be contacted for such purposes.
  * To carry out our obligations arising from any contracts entered into between you and us.
  * To allow you to participate in interactive features of our service, when you choose to do so.
  * To notify you about changes to our service.

### Disclosure of your information

We may disclose your personal information to third parties if we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to comply with any legal obligation, our customers, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organisations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

### Your Rights

You have the right to ask us to remove any data we have on our site from you at any time.

### Access to Information

The Act gives you the right to access information held about you. Your right of access can be exercised in accordance with the Act.

### Changes to our privacy policy

Any changes we may make to our privacy policy in the future will be posted on this page and, where appropriate, notified to you by e-mail. However, we advise that you check this page regularly to keep up to date with any necessary changes.

### Contact

Questions, comments and requests regarding this privacy policy are welcomed and should be addressed to [hello@cloud66.com](mailto:hello@cloud66.com)
